nse.com.ng 2019-11-13

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Please read this Privacy Policy before you may become a business or personal user of this Website, www.nse.com.ng. 

**INTRODUCTION**  

This Privacy Policy sets out how The Exchange collects, uses, stores, shares and protects any information that you give The Exchange when you use this Website. It applies to this Website and all its applications, services, tools and content regardless of how you access or use them.

The Exchange is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this Website; you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**CONSENT**

You accept this Privacy Policy when you sign up for access or use the products, services, content, features, technologies or functions offered on this Website and all related sites, applications, and services.

###  **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

 _ **Personal Information We Collect Directly from You**_

The Exchange collects Personal Information from you when you use this Website. The type of Personal Information that we collect from you depends on your particular interaction with the Website. We require you to register on the Website to access certain features. When we do, we may collect the following information from you during the registration process: 

  * Full Name;
  * Email Address;
  * Phone Number;
  * Gender;
  * House Address;
  * Details of Next of Kin;
  * User name and password that you create.

If you choose to purchase a product or procure service through the Website, we may collect your credit or debit card information. Currently, we use third party service providers to process your bank verification number, credit and debit card transactions on our behalf. The third-party service providers will collect your contact information (such as your name, address, and e-mail, bank verification number,) bank or financial information (such as debit or credit card number and expiration date) in accordance with the provisions of a written contract between The Exchange and the third party. We will be verifying your BVN data and by your use of this Website, you consent to the validation of your BVN data. 

We may also collect the information you provide us including but not limited to information on web forms, account update information and correspondence with the Website support services team. Information obtained through voluntary submissions (e.g., responses to surveys, requests for information on The Exchange's Website or those of The Exchange's advertisers/marketing partners) and review of Website usage patterns survey responses, customer enquiries and other means may also be collected and used by us. The Exchange will only collect information that is necessary for the provision of the product or service that you have subscribed to. 

_**Personal Information We Collect Automatically  **_

The Exchange may use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies to collect information about you automatically as you use the Website. This information includes information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone, POS or other electronic access devices. The automatically collected information includes but is not limited to data about the pages you access, computer IP address, device ID or unique identifier, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, mobile network information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, referral URL, ad data, the dates and times of your use of the Website and standard web log data. We may combine this information with other information that we collect about you.

 _ **Personal Information We Collect from Third Parties**_

We also collect information about you from third party sources such as identity verification services, and analytics providers in accordance with the provisions of a written contract between The Exchange and the third party. The categories of information that we collect about you from other sources include:

  * Full Name
  * Date of Birth);
  * Contact Details (e.g. phone number, email address, and/or mobile number).

Please note that we may be required by law to collect and use certain Personal Information about you. And we may need to collect and use Personal Information to enter into or fulfil a contract with you. Failure to provide this information may prevent or delay the fulfilment of our obligations in these circumstances.

 **How The Exchange uses Information it Collects**

We primarily use your Personal Information to provide the requisite Services to you and to respond to your inquiries. We also may use your Personal Information as follows:

  * To communicate with you, including to respond to your comments or requests for information, to request feedback on our products and services, and to notify you about changes to your subscriptions/ registration or to the services you use.
  * To help The Exchange understand you, to tailor and enhance our product and service offerings, anticipate and resolve problems with any products or services supplied to you, create products or services that may meet your needs.
  * To provide access to restricted pages or contents of the Website
  * To comply with legal and/or regulatory requirements and cooperate with regulators and law enforcement bodies.
  * To facilitate your activity and to identify you when you log into your account on our Website.
  * To send you marketing communications and advertising in line with your communications preferences and where permitted by applicable law about products, services and opportunities that we believe would be of interest to you, including products and services offered by third parties.

To protect our rights, your rights, and the rights of others, and to meet our own high standards of business practice.

The services of the third party may be employed to help us in certain areas, such as website hosting, marketing and market researching. In some cases, the third party may receive your information. However, at all times we will endeavour to keep control and be responsible for the use of your information. By providing The Exchange with your Personal Information, you consent to our transferring of your information to countries or jurisdictions which may not provide the same level of data protection as us. If we do make such a transfer, we will, if appropriate, put a contract in place that imposes obligations on our counterparties to protect your information. Each time you provide us with Personal Information we aim to let you know how we intend to use it and ask you to give your consent to such use.

 **SECURITY AND PROTECTION**  

Personal Information collected will be held securely and will only be kept for as long as is reasonably necessary in the circumstances you are registered; to use the Website or for as long as you use the service or product that you are subscribed to, unless you have provided us with your consent to use the data for any additional purposes. We take the security of the Website and the information you provide very seriously, and we will take all appropriate technical measures using recognized security procedures and tools in accordance with good industry practice to protect your Personal Information. We have reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and interception by third parties of the information under our control, but, to the extent allowed by law, The Exchange assumes no liability for any damages you may suffer as a result of interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet. Whilst we use all reasonable endeavours to protect your security in the manner described above, we consider that it is only appropriate to advise users that data transmission over the Internet and the World Wide Web cannot be guaranteed as 100% secure, and therefore that you use the Website at your own risk. 

 **YOUR SECURITY OBLIGATIONS**

Your online access to certain of your Personal Information may be protected with a password you select. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (such as letters, phone calls or email messages). You have an obligation to keep your user ID, password and Personal Information secure. As part of maintaining this obligation we recommend that you do the following:

  * Keep your user ID and password confidential;
  * Utilize a unique password and change it frequently;
  * Make sure others are not watching you enter your user ID and/or password on your keyboard when using protected elements of the Digital Services; and
  * Do not leave your computer unattended while logged onto the Website. After you finished accessing your information, exit the protected area.

 **DO WE USE COOKIES?**  

Yes. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Cookies are features included in your browser and will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the Website, in particular when you complete any form on the Website. However, a cookie does not provide us with any Personal Information. Therefore, if you have not supplied us with any Personal Information, you can still browse our site anonymously. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of the Website. Cookies on the Website are not used to capture or store personal data from browsers to the site, other than to log your IP address and session information such as the duration of the visit to our site and the nature of the browser used. This information is used only for administration of the site system and in the compilation of statistics used by The Exchange. Cookies may be required to allow you to access and participate in certain areas of the Website. Once you have closed your browser, this type of cookie is deactivated. The majority of browsers will allow you to alter the settings used for cookies and to disable and enable them as you require. If you do not want cookies and for further general information on cookies you may wish to visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.  

 **CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  

We will not sell, distribute or lease your Personal Information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

 **REMEDIES FOR VIOLATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY** ** **

Any person subject to this Privacy Policy who is found to be in breach of this privacy policy by: 

a.      failure to implement safeguards required by the Nigeria Data Protection Regulation 2019 or any of the security measures provided in this Policy;

b.      failure to mitigate the damage once it has occurred; or

c.       failure to timely notify the affected individuals shall be liable, in addition to any other civil liabilities, to the penalties provided in the Nigerian Data Protection Regulation.

 **​CONTACTING THE EXCHANGE** ** **

Our customer service contacts are **** contactcenter@nse.com.ng and +234 700 225 5673.  We shall endeavour to respond to enquiries/issues sent to/made to these service contacts within 48 hours. ** **

 **GOVERNING LANGUAGE**

These Terms and Conditions, and the contents of this Website are available in English 

**GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION**

By accessing the services on this Website, you agree to be governed by the laws of the Federal Republic of Nigeria and the Nigeria Data Protection Regulation 2019. The laws of the Federal Republic of Nigeria will govern all matters relating to this Terms and Conditions and the use, or inability to use the Website, and shall apply without regard to the principles of conflict of laws. 

You agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the Courts in the Federal Republic of Nigeria. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, The Exchange may seek recourse in any jurisdiction worldwide in order to restrain the unlawful use of the Website or any material contained in the Website.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 12, 2019
